{
    "data": {
        "title": "JavaScript Flashcards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "What language are Express apps written in?",
                "hint": "It starts with a \"J\"",
                "answer": "JavaScript"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is one way a website can store data in a user's browser?",
                "hint": "They are delicious with milk",
                "answer": "Cookies"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a common way to shorten the response object's name inside middleware?",
                "hint": "It has the same abbreviation as \"resolution\"",
                "answer": "res"
            },
            {
                "question": "How many different values can booleans have?",
                "hint": "Think: binary",
                "answer": "2"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which HTML element can contain JavaScript?",
                "hint": "It starts with an \"s\"",
                "answer": "<script>"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is routing and how routing works in Express.js?",
                "hint": "How does an application respond to a client request?",
                "answer": "Routing refers to determining how an application responds to a client request to a particular endpoint, which is a URI (or path) and a specific HTTP request method (GET, POST, and so on)."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is an application-level middleware?",
                "hint": "Does it apply on all routes or a particular route?",
                "answer": "It's kind of middleware method that is bound to the app Object using app.use() method. It applies on all routes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is Express.js?",
                "hint": "",
                "answer": "Express.js is a free open-source, light-weight node js based web application framework"
            },
            {
                "question": "How to install Express.js?",
                "hint": "",
                "answer": "$ mkdir myapp then $ cd myapp then $ npm init then entry point: (index.js) then $ npm install express --save"
            },
            {
                "question": "What function arguments are available to Express.js route handlers?",
                "hint": "The first two arguments start with 'r'",
                "answer": "req, res, next"
            }
        ]
    }
}